<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
      <string-array name="question_inspire_question">
      	<item>Whatever you can do or dream you can, begin it. Boldness has genius, magic and power in it. Begin it now.</item>
      	<item>I long to accomplish a great and noble task, but it is my chief duty to accomplish humble tasks as though they were great and noble.</item>
      	<item>Never bend your head. Always hold it high. Look the world straight in the face.</item>
				<item>Face your deficiencies and acknowledge them; but do not let them master you. Let them teach you patience, sweetness, insight.</item>
				<item>Only through experience of trial and suffering can the soul be strengthened, vision cleared, ambition inspired, and success achieved.</item>
				<item>None are so old as those who have outlived enthusiasm.</item>
				<item>I know of no more encouraging fact than the unquestionable ability of man to elevate his life by conscious endeavor.</item>
				<item>In the long run, men hit only what they aim at. Therefore, they had better aim at something high.</item>
				<item>Whether you think that you can, or that you can\'t, you are usually right.</item>
				<item>He is rich or poor according to what he is, not according to what he has.</item>
				<item>The difference between perseverance and obstinacy is that one often comes from a strong will, and the other from a strong won\'t.</item>
				<item>The goal is the same: life itself; and the price is the same; life itself.</item>
				<item>Each of us is great insofar as we perceive and act on the infinite possibilities which lie undiscovered and unrecognized about us.</item>
				<item>Let us not look back in anger or forward in fear, but around in awareness.</item>
				<item>Vision without action is a daydream. Action without vision is a nightmare.</item>
				<item>If you are aware of your weaknesses and are constantly learning, your potential is virtually limitless.</item>
				<item>Shoot for the moon. Even if you miss, you will land amongst the stars.</item>
				<item>The one unchangeable certainty is that nothing is unchangeable or certain.</item>
				<item>The mind is its own place, and in itself, can make heaven of Hell, and a hell of Heaven.</item>
				<item>There\'s only us, there\'s only this, forget regret, or life is yours to miss. No other road, no other way, no day but today.</item>
				<item>As a rule, men worry more about what they can\'t see than about what they can.</item>
				<item>Never frown because you never know who might be falling in love with your smile.</item>
				<item>Continuous effort, not strength or intelligence, is the key to unlocking our potential.</item>
				<item>Ability is what you\'re capable of doing. Motivation determines what you do. Attitude determines how well you do it.</item>
				<item>As human beings, our greatness lies not so much in being able to remake the world... as in being able to remake ourselves.</item>
				<item>The men who build the future are those who know that greater things are yet to come, and that they themselves will help bring them about.</item>
				<item>It is not only for what we do that we are held responsible, but also for what we do not do.</item>
				<item>Take time to deliberate, but when the time for action has arrived, stop thinking and go in.</item>
				<item>Opportunity... often it comes disguised in the form of misfortune, or temporary defeat.</item>
				<item>Every problem has in it the seeds of its own solution. If you don\'t have any problems, you don\'t have any seeds.</item>
				<item>The truly important things in life - love, beauty, and one\'s own uniqueness - are constantly being overlooked.</item>
				<item>Each man has his own vocation; his talent is his call. There is one direction in which all space is open to him.</item>
				<item>That which we persist in doing becomes easier - not that the nature of the task has changed, but our ability to do has increased.</item>
				<item>Do not follow where the path may lead. Go instead where there is no path and leave a trail.</item>
				<item>Don\'t let life discourage you; everyone who got where he is had to begin where he was.</item>
				<item>To travel hopefully is a better thing than to arrive, and the true success is to labour.</item>
				<item>Don\'t judge each day by the harvest you reap, but by the seeds you plant.</item>
				<item>What you think of yourself is much more important than what others think of you.</item>
				<item>If we did the things we are capable of, we would astound ourselves.</item>
				<item>The rung of a ladder was never meant to rest upon, but only to hold a man\'s foot long enough to enable him to put the other somewhat higher.</item>
				<item>Nothing can stop the man with the right mental attitude from achieving his goal; nothing on earth can help with man with the wrong mental attitude.</item>
				<item>The greatest pleasure in life is in doing what people say you cannot do.</item>
				<item>A pessimist sees the difficulty in every opportunity; an optimist sees the opportunity in every difficulty.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>