<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
      <string-array name="question_reading_question">
        <item>It’s a great advantage not to drink among hard drinking people.</item>
        <item>Better to sleep with a sober cannibal than a drunk Christian.</item>
        <item>Your best days are ahead of you. The movie starts when the guy gets sober and puts his life back together; it doesn\'t end there.</item>
        <item>When you quit drinking you stop waiting.</item>
        <item>There is no better high than discovery.</item>
        <item>We have learned that the satisfaction of instincts cannot be the sole aim of our lives.</item>
        <item>We want ecstasy as a way of life, not a liver-poisoning alcoholiday from it.</item>
        <item>Life is very interesting... in the end, some of your greatest pains, become your greatest strengths.</item>
        <item>I am not bound to win, but I am bound to be true. I am not bound to succeed, but I am bound to live up to what light I have.</item>
        <item>Always bear in mind that your own resolution to success is more important than any other one thing.</item>
        <item>If at first an idea isn\'t absurd there is no hope for it.</item>
        <item>Imagination is more important than knowledge.</item>
        <item>In the middle of difficulty lies opportunity.</item>
        <item>There are only two ways to live your life. One is though nothing is a miracle. The other is though everything is a miracle.</item>
        <item>Reputation is what folks think you are. Personality is what you seem to be. Character is what you really are.</item>
        <item>One doesn\'t discover new lands without consenting to lose sight of the shore for a very long time.</item>
        <item>You must pay the price if you wish to secure the blessings.</item>
        <item>When everything seems like an uphill struggle, just think of the view from the top.</item>
        <item>Your altitude is determined by your attitude.</item>
        <item>Champions in any field have made a habit of doing what others find boring or uncomfortable.</item>
        <item>Those who follow the crowd are quickly lost in it.</item>
        <item>What you become is more important than what you accomplish.</item>
        <item>No individual raindrop considers itself responsible for the flood.</item>
        <item>The desire not to be anything is the desire not to be.</item>
				<item>No one\'s happiness but my own is in my power to achieve or to destroy.</item>
				<item>Happiness is that state of consciousness which proceeds from the achievement of one\'s values.</item>
				<item>No man or woman is uniformly successful… we must all expect a rather high percentage of failure in the things we attempt.</item>
				<item>Well done is better than well said.</item>
				<item>To trust yourself to test your limits. That is the courage to succeed.</item>
				<item>Decide that you want it more than you are afraid of it.</item>
				<item>Do not think that what your thoughts dwell on does not matter. Your thoughts are making you.</item>
				<item>The man who makes no mistakes does not usually make anything.</item>
				<item>We must learn our limits. We are all something, but none of us are everything.</item>
				<item>It\'s not the situation…… it\'s your reaction to the situation.</item>
				<item>Success is to be measured not so much by the position that one has reached in life, as by the obstacles one has overcome trying to succeed.</item>
				<item>Our first and last love is - self-love.</item>
				<item>Move out of your comfort zone. You can only grow if you are willing to feel awkward and uncomfortable when you try something new.</item>
				<item>Sometimes when I consider what tremendous consequences come from little things… I am tempted to think… there are no little things.</item>
				<item>The less effort, the faster and more powerful you will be.</item>
				<item>Experience shows that success is due less to ability than to zeal. The winner is he who gives himself to his work, body and soul.</item>
				<item>A man who dares to waste one hour of life has not discovered the value of life.</item>
				<item>The important thing is this: To be able at any moment to sacrifice what we are for what we could become.</item>
				<item>Better to light one small candle than to curse the darkness.</item>
				<item>Life is just a blank slate, what matters most is what you write on it.</item>
				<item>Drugs are merely the most obvious form of addiction in our society. Drug addiction is one of the things that undermines traditional values.</item>
				<item>The big shots are only the little shots who keep shooting.</item>
				<item>Natural ability without education has more often raised a man to glory and virtue than education without natural ability.</item>
				<item>The proof of a well-trained mind is that it rejoices in which is good and grieves at the opposite.</item>
				<item>It\'s the constant and determined effort that breaks down all resistance, sweeps away all obstacles.</item>
				<item>There are no secrets to success. It is the result of preparation, hard work, learning from failure.</item>
				<item>The superior man is distressed by the limitations of his ability; he is not distressed by the fact that men do not recognize the ability that he has.</item>
				<item>Remember, today is the tomorrow you worried about yesterday.</item>
				<item>Take a chance! All life is a chance. The man who goes the furthest is generally the one who is willing to do and dare.</item>
				<item>People rarely succeed unless they have fun in what they are doing.</item>
				<item>The successful man will profit from his mistakes and try again in a different way.</item>
				<item>Try out your ideas by visualizing them in action.</item>
				<item>The only limits on human achievement are self-imposed.</item>
				<item>There are two kinds of failures: those who thought and never did, and those who did and never thought.</item>
				<item>The ultimate measure of a man is not where he stands in moments of comfort and convenience, but where he stands at times of challenge and controversy.</item>
				<item>He that wrestles with us strengthens our nerves and sharpens our skill. Our antagonist is our helper.</item>
				<item>One man has enthusiasm for 30 minutes, another for 30 days, but it is the man who has it for 30 years who makes a success of his life.</item>
				<item>No-one can make you feel inferior without your consent.</item>
				<item>Every day, in every way, I am getting better and better.</item>
				<item>The artist is nothing without the gift, but the gift is nothing without work.</item>
				<item>The soul should always stand ajar, ready to welcome the ecstatic experience.</item>
				<item>Do not spoil what you have by desiring what you have not; but remember that what you have was once among the things only hoped for.</item>
				<item>Knowledge itself is power.</item>
				<item>Convictions are the mainsprings of action, the driving powers of life. What a man lives are his convictions.</item>
				<item>Why not go out on a limb? Isn\'t that where the fruit is?</item>
				<item>If a man does his best, what else is there?</item>
				<item>Some men see things as they are and ask why. Others dream things that never were and ask why not</item>
				<item>It\'s never too late to be what you might have been.</item>
				<item>We can accomplish almost anything within our ability if we but think we can.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>